valuemystuffnow.com 2012-06-30

# Privacy Policy VALUEMYSTUFFNOW.COM

VALUEMYSTUFFNOW.COM considers the privacy and protection of its clients' personal data to be of utmost importance. To ensure that you feel confident about providing us with your personal information and photographs of your items when communicating with us and using our services, we outline below our practices in relation to the collection and use of personal data.

**Purposes**  
VALUEMYSTUFFNOW.COM will collect, record, store and use your personal data but only to enable you to be provided with extra services we offer, special deals or other events. It is possible to opt out of this by emailing us at info@valuemystuff.com.

**Privacy**  
We will not share your Personal Data with anyone outside VALUEMYSTUFFNOW.COM without your consent except as set out in this policy. We may from time to time however need to disclose your personal data to agents or contractors of VALUEMYSTUFFNOW.COM to enable us to process transactions or communicate with you or as required or permitted by law. Where we do so it will be on the basis that they are required to keep the information confidential and will not use the information for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for VALUEMYSTUFFNOW.COM.

**Security**  
Any personal data you provide to us is securely stored in a database held by VALUEMYSTUFFNOW.COM in the United Kingdom to which only authorised VALUEMYSTUFFNOW.COM employees and agents have access. We have put in place administrative measures to ensure that the access which VALUEMYSTUFFNOW.COM employees and agents have to personal data on our server is limited to the extent necessary in order to perform their functions. All our employees are required to sign a confidentiality agreement in which they agree to treat personal data as strictly confidential.

**Web-site**  
In general, you may browse our Internet site anonymously. However, when asked to value an item we require the collection of some personally identifying information, such as your name, address, and, when appropriate, your credit information. For transactions over the VALUEMYSTUFFNOW.COM web-site involving particularly confidential information, such as credit card numbers and accounting information, VALUEMYSTUFFNOW.COM will employ accepted transmission and storage protocols, such as encryption, to prevent this information from being disclosed. This means that when you type in sensitive information such as credit card details, it will be automatically converted into codes before being securely sent to us over the Internet. This information will be used for processing transactions but may also be used for internal data processing, such as compiling statistical information about your interests and the use of our Internet site. As a service to you, we may also use this information to customize the content we offer.

**Email**  
In order to provide you with our valuation certificate and timely notice about upcoming offers and events, VALUEMYSTUFFNOW.COM may send you email notices. At the bottom of each email you will be provided with the option to opt out of such notifications by email. At any time, you may also send an email to info@stgeorgevaluations.com and request that your email address be removed from our lists.

**Business Relationships**  
The VALUEMYSTUFFNOW.COM site may contain links to other Web sites. None of the information that you provide to us will be transmitted to other Web sites. VALUEMYSTUFFNOW.COM is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Cookies**  
VALUEMYSTUFFNOW.COM may also use on its Internet properties a personalization technology called a "cookie." A cookie is a small text file placed on your computer's hard disk that identifies your browser software to a Web site. Cookies allow us to track when you enter, leave, and re-enter our sites and what path you take through our sites. In doing this, we can provide you with a more personalised experience and better use of our site.

**Exceptions**  
While we will not voluntarily disclose your personal data, except as set out in this policy, we may disclose such information if we are required to do so by a Court Order, if we are requested by government or law enforcement authorities, if we are required to do so pursuant to other legal processes, or if it becomes necessary to protect the rights or property of VALUEMYSTUFFNOW.COM. Your data will be retained for six years in accordance with current data retention guidelines. If you would like a copy of personal data held about you, please contact info@stgeorgevaluations.com for further information. We charge £10 per request and will respond within a maximum of 40 days.

**Contact**  
If you have any queries in relation to the use and protection of your personal data please contact us at [info@valuemystuff.com](mailto:info@valuemystuffnow.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy) or call us on 0207 148 7040.

#### It's quick and easy to get an expert valuation...

##### 1\. You upload photos

You upload some photos of your item and add any information you have.

##### 2\. We assign an expert

We assign your item to the appropriate expert from our experienced team

##### 3\. You receive a valuation

Within 48 hours you will receive a full valuation report or your money back

 **Get a valuation**    
 **Learn how it works**
